<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on Shadows</title>
    <link>http://shadows.ajbourg.com/pages/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on Shadows</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://shadows.ajbourg.com/pages/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>About Shadows</title>
      <link>http://shadows.ajbourg.com/pages/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://shadows.ajbourg.com/pages/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;There are some people in the world that when you interact with them, you feel just a little closer to God. Maybe it&amp;rsquo;s their compassion, or their love, or their encouragement. Maybe it&amp;rsquo;s their love for Christ. Whatever it is &amp;ndash; even if you can&amp;rsquo;t quite put your finger on it &amp;ndash; you walk away from them feeling like, &amp;ldquo;If there is a God &amp;ndash; I hope He&amp;rsquo;s a little like that.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take the best people in your life &amp;ndash; whether that&amp;rsquo;s one person or one-hundred &amp;ndash; add them up, and I think God &lt;em&gt;is&lt;/em&gt; a lot like that. God puts people in our lives that reflect His heart and character and He whispers in our ear: &amp;ldquo;This is a shadow of who I Am.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s my hope that God reveals Himself more and more to me &amp;ndash; His purpose and His personality. And while I can sit on my hands and hope that God just appears, part of the process is discovery. God loves it when His people seek His face and find out who He really is.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And part of my discovery of God involves writing. &amp;ldquo;I write because I don&amp;rsquo;t know what I think until I read what I say.&amp;rdquo; (Flannery O&amp;rsquo;Connor) It&amp;rsquo;s not the only discovery, and it&amp;rsquo;s not even the biggest part. But I want to explore who God is, and what He&amp;rsquo;s like by writing down my discovery.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What I write can only ever be a feint image, a dim reflection &amp;ndash; or just a &lt;strong&gt;shadow&lt;/strong&gt; of what God is really like.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>