<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Shadows on Shadows</title>
    <link>http://shadows.ajbourg.com/shadow/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Shadows on Shadows</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://shadows.ajbourg.com/shadow/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Overwhelming Love</title>
      <link>http://shadows.ajbourg.com/shadow/001-overwhelming-love/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://shadows.ajbourg.com/shadow/001-overwhelming-love/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Since he did not spare even his own Son but gave him up for us all, won&amp;rsquo;t he also give us everything else?&lt;/em&gt; &amp;ndash;Romans 8:32 (NLT)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I often hear myself say preposterous things like, &amp;ldquo;I wonder if God really loves me.&amp;rdquo; Or, its cousin, &amp;ldquo;If God really loved me, he would (&lt;em&gt;fill in the blank&lt;/em&gt;).&amp;rdquo; But so often I forget that God has already given me &lt;em&gt;everything&lt;/em&gt;. God already demonstrated how much He loves me by sacrificing His son on a Roman cross. Theologians have spent centuries trying to explain why this was necessary theologically, but I want to consider it from a different angle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If God really and truly loves me &amp;ndash; because He made me, what is the one thing He could do to show it? If He used His fingers to write in the sky, &amp;ldquo;AJ, I love you,&amp;rdquo; you may eventually convince me I was crazy or seeing things. If He answered a prayer, that may work &amp;hellip; until I have another prayer. If He gave me a lot of money or the best clothes or the shiniest toys &amp;ndash; that would work only until the shininess wore off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But if He gave His Son as a way of saying, &amp;ldquo;I am willing to do whatever it takes to reconcile you back to Me&amp;rdquo; &amp;ndash; how could we ever possibly answer that and ask of Him, &amp;ldquo;What have You done for me, lately?&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Christ bore the punishment for my death and shame. He became my sin &amp;ndash; trading His crown for a Roman cross and nails. And as He completed the assignment His Father gave Him, He made it possible for me and for you to enter from death to life. From condemnation to righteousness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The next time I wonder if God really loves me or if God has finally given up on me &amp;ndash; may I remember that God has already given His Son in exchange for bringing me back. And there is nothing more God could possibly do to demonstrate His love for me.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dead to sin. Alive in Christ.</title>
      <link>http://shadows.ajbourg.com/shadow/dead-to-sin-alive-in-christ/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://shadows.ajbourg.com/shadow/dead-to-sin-alive-in-christ/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Even so consider yourselves to be dead to sin, but alive to God in Christ Jesus.&lt;/em&gt; (Romans 6:11, NASB)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like a chicken with its head cut off, it takes a little while for our sin to realize it is dead. Christ has killed it in our record, imputing His righteousness on our behalf. But our mortal body, so used to sin, hasn&amp;rsquo;t figured out that it is no longer mastered by sin but mastered by Christ instead. I like the idea of dying daily. Every day, I need to make it a habit to die. To have my fleshly desires crucified. To remind myself and my flesh that I am no longer controlled by sin or the evil desires of my heart.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because sometimes I forget. I think I am controlled by the wickedness of my heart. But the heart deceives. It lies. It controls. God has removed sin&amp;rsquo;s grip on my heart. And may I practice righteous so that I mortify my sin and slowly but surely rob it of its effectiveness over my heart and my life. I need to weaken it. To kill it so it never rules my heart again.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forgiven</title>
      <link>http://shadows.ajbourg.com/shadow/forgiven/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://shadows.ajbourg.com/shadow/forgiven/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Then He said to her, “Your sins have been forgiven.”&lt;/em&gt; (Luke 7:48, NASB)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As I read those words the other day, I cried. This woman came to Jesus and her deepest need was met by him. She was loved, accepted and forgiven. Yes she came to him and washed his feet and kissed his feet, she adored Jesus. But truly she had nothing she could offer to Him, except her devotion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Absent from the dialog is any pretense of conversation. No promises that she will give up sinning forever. She loved Him and He forgave her. That is beautiful. Spectacular. Undeserved and unmerited.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And what brought tears to my eye is the realization that I am that woman. As much as I might like to pretend otherwise, I have nothing to offer Jesus. I can love Him. But I can&amp;rsquo;t even promise Him my faithfulness through the end of the hour. And get this, He loves me anyway. He forgives me anyway. I don&amp;rsquo;t need to make a dozen promises I can&amp;rsquo;t even keep through lunchtime tomorrow. I just need to love Him. And He loves and forgives me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;rsquo;t deserve that. No one does. And yet He loves us still.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>